# **Molly Crowhurst**

Email: Mollycrowhurst1@gmail.com

Ph: (+61) 416 299 904

Location: Middle Park, QLD, 4074

# About me:

I am an 18 year old transgender woman who recently graduated high school. My specific background and set of skills mean not only am I technologically adept, but I know how to help out other LGBT+ people and how to help them feel more comfortable in different working environments.

#### **Education:**

2017-2022

# **Centenary State High School**

- QCE
- Certificate II in Skills for Work and Vocational Pathways
- 8 years of weekly band practice (started 2015)

2020

# **TAFE Acacia Ridge**

5 week long trade taster course which resulted in:

- Stick welding experience
- Basic light automotive maintenance experience
- Basic knowledge of ballasting and rail infrastructure
- White card for Construction Induction

#### Work Experience:

09/2022 - 01/2023 12/9/2023 - current

### Casual Staff - CSHS Uniform Shop

My duties in the Uniform Shop include but are not limited to: interacting with customers, working with money, sorting and packing stock, standing for long periods, working with stock reports (both physical and digital), transferring data from physical documents to digital documents.

### **Software Experience:**

- Office Suite & Alternatives (e.g. Google Suite, Libre Office)
- Adobe Suite & Alternatives (e.g. GIMP)
- Unity & Blender
- VR based programs (e.g. Oculus app, Steam VR)
- POS Programs
- Linux, Ubuntu (GUI and Command line)

#### **Achievements:**

Young ICT Explorers 2022, SE QLD: 2<sup>nd</sup> Place

Installing personal server on laptop running Linux (Ubuntu)

#### **Extra Qualifications:**

- White Card (Construction Induction)
- Blue Card (Working with / around Children)
- Drivers License (Learners, will be moving on to Provisional shortly)

#### **References:**

Circa 2023

Shweta Gupta - CSHS Uniform Shop Convener

Email: sgupt29@eq.edu.au

Molly Crowhurst - Resume